https://animalfarmfoundation.org/animal-farm-foundation-privacy-policy/

Effective Date:  December 2018
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Animal Farm Foundation and our website; http://www.animalfarmfoundation.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:
What information we collect;With whom it is shared;How it can be corrected;How it is secured;How policy changes will be communicated; andHow to address concerns over misuse of personal data.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We may also collect non-identifiable information, which we may use to make improvements to this website and enhance the overall user experience. See “Cookies” below.
We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about our work, new campaigns, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at 845.868.7559 or info@animalfarmfoundation.org:
See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data
Orders
We request information from you on our order and donation forms. To buy from us or donate to us, you must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number with its expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your transaction. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you. We do not store your credit card information on our servers.
Sharing
Occasionally, we may we use an outside shipping company to ship orders or direct mail, and we use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and donations. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to improve your access to our site and helps us identify repeat visitors. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Notification of Changes
We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and will publish the most current version on our website. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 845.868.7559 or via email at info@animalfarmfoundation.org.
Search for:
Recent Posts
A Special Thanks As We Reflect on 2020
Dog Advocates Shouldn’t Be So Quick to Celebrate the “Win” in Denver
Are Pet-Friendly Cities Really that Pet-Friendly
Help Willow Heal
We Don’t Need Pet Food Pantries, We Need Collaborative Community Resources
